<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Tyler Horan</title>
    <link>https://tylerhoran.org/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Tyler Horan</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 02 Nov 2019 08:47:11 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://tylerhoran.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Digital Tools for The Analog Ethnographer</title>
      <link>https://tylerhoran.org/blog/digital-ethnographic-tools-for-social-research/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Nov 2019 08:47:11 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tylerhoran.org/blog/digital-ethnographic-tools-for-social-research/</guid>
      <description>Ethonographic and interview methods for the social sciences have been around since the professionalization of the academic fields themselves. The idea of moving into a social field and interacting with participants can, without a doubt, yield rich data that other quantitative and survey methods leave on the table.
A tension exists for the researcher or being in the moment and storaging traces of that moment for analysis and data presentation in scholarly work.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to keep up with the scientific literature</title>
      <link>https://tylerhoran.org/blog/journal-discovery/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Nov 2019 08:47:11 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tylerhoran.org/blog/journal-discovery/</guid>
      <description>There&#39;s a lot of information out there. The best place to start is to make two lists (one of which is probably already available online).
 What are the top journals in your field? What are the top journals in your field that cater to your research interests?  Now you have your lists. They may or may not have the same journals on them. The combination of your lists should be atleast 10 and at most 50.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://tylerhoran.org/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tylerhoran.org/about/</guid>
      <description>I am a Computational Social Scientist. Much of my research has been about social networks and the social impacts of online technology. My current work focuses on the use of large scale social network data to examine national and inter-national cultural behavior. I also work on techniques and methods for web application development and architecture, data collection and visualization.
Most of my publications and working papers are available on this site, along with information about teaching, CS and Social Research resources and occasional writing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://tylerhoran.org/publications/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tylerhoran.org/publications/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://tylerhoran.org/resources/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tylerhoran.org/resources/</guid>
      <description>Journaled Track your journal subscriptions in one place and download the latest content. While searching through library databases and cross-database indexes is a great way to do research on a topic, when it comes to staying up to date on all the latest research from your discipline&#39;s popular journals, there&#39;s no easy way to do it. Rather than try and subscribe to &amp;ldquo;new issue&amp;rdquo; alerts, Journaled monitors CrossRef for new DOIs from your subscribed journals.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>