<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Teachings on Tyler Horan</title>
    <link>https://tylerhoran.org/teaching/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Teachings on Tyler Horan</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 02 Nov 2019 08:47:11 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://tylerhoran.org/teaching/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Intro to Computational Social Science</title>
      <link>https://tylerhoran.org/teaching/intro-comp-soc-sci/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Nov 2019 08:47:11 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tylerhoran.org/teaching/intro-comp-soc-sci/</guid>
      <description>With an increasing amount of data on every aspect of our daily activity—from what we buy, to where we travel, to whom we know—we are able to measure human behavior with precision largely thought impossible just a decade ago, creating an unprecedented opportunity to address longstanding questions in the social sciences. Leveraging this information, however, requires both scalable computational tools, and understanding how the substantive scientific questions should drive the data analysis.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Programming Abstractions</title>
      <link>https://tylerhoran.org/teaching/programming-abstractions/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Nov 2019 08:47:11 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tylerhoran.org/teaching/programming-abstractions/</guid>
      <description>This course is the natural successor to Programming Methodology and covers such advanced programming topics as recursion, algorithmic analysis, and data abstraction using the Python programming language. Programming Abstractions assumes that you already have familiarity with good programming style and software engineering issues (at the level of Programming Methodology), and that you can use this understanding as a foundation on which to tackle new topics in programming and data abstraction.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>